So I have a very genuine question for supporters of Jasmine Crockett in Texas.
What are you willing to do to get her through the primary?
She was always going to be a long shot because she is a black woman with a very limited record in a state that is 100 percent racist and zio and gerrymandered at the hootenanny.
Like even before it was exposed that she is 100 percent in support of Israel, even before many of the people in her state who are very unrelenting on that fact said we will not vote for her.
It was still going to be a long shot.
You were still going to need to get behind her in a very real way.
Did you think that that was simply just voting?
Did you think that you simply voting for Jasmine Crockett was going to be enough for her to win the primary, let alone the Senate seat?
What are you prepared to do to actually support this candidate versus trying to shame those of us who do not support her support of an apartheid genocide state that is actually using your tax dollars?
Support a real one.